mirascreen.com 2016-06-11

# 无标题文档

## Your privacy is important to Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. So we developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information.   
Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.  
You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Actions Microelectronic Co., Ltd. or our affiliated companies. We and our affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.  You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have.  
Here are some examples of the types of personal information we may collect and how we may use it.

### What personal information we collect

  1. When you are using EZCast/EZCast Pro related products, we may collect a variety of information, including how you use the product, what feature you use & use time, device name, email address and location…etc., but not including some confidential and sensitive information like your name, age, gender, ID number or credit card number.
  2. When you share your content with family or friends by usingour products, we may collect your socialnetwork contacts like Facebook, Weibo…etc.

### How we use your personal information

  1. The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on our latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. And it will also be used to create, develop, operate and improve our product quality, services, content and advertising.
  2. We may use your information to post news, updated information or share content to your socialnetwork friends.
  3. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  4. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications.
  5. If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.
  6. We will use your information to reply your questions or help to resolve problems you encounter while using our products.

## Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  1. We may collect information such as country code,area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where our product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.
  2. We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website, EZCast/EZCast Pro website, EZCast/EZCast Pro services, and our store and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

## Cookies and Other Technologies

Our website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.  
We and our partners use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. You may still see ads related to the content on a web page or in an application or based on other non-personal information.  
We and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with us more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your location and language will let us deliver you the correspondingwebpage. Knowing your country and language − and if you are an educator, your school − helps us provide a customized and more useful web experience. Knowing your devices information will help us to register your product and provide better customer services.  
As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  
We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may also use this information in our marketing and advertising services.  
In some of our webpage or notifications, email messages, we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on some websites. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links.  
Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers. 

## Data Usage time

It will start from installing or using our EZCast/EZCast pro related HW/SW products, and will be expired after you remove/uninstall it.

## Disclosure to Third Parties

At times we may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with our company to provide products and services, or that help our market to customers. For example, when you purchase and activate your EZCast device, you authorize us and your carrier to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by us and your carrier’s respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by us to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

### Service Providers

We shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever we operate.

### Others

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for us to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.  
We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

## Protection of Personal Information

We will take the security of your personal information very seriously.  When your personal data is stored by us, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures. When you use our products, services, or applications or post on EZCast forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

## Location-Based Services

To provide location-based services on our products, we and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer, smartphone or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by us and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, we may share geographic location with advertisement providers when you opt in to their location services.

## Third-Party Sites and Services

Our websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

## Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

## Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please [contact us](http://www.actions-micro.com/).  
We may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.
